

CONTACT ME AT

- Bekasi, Indonesia
- adihernawan5@gmail.com
- https://adiher.com/

SKILLS SUMMARY

- •••• PHP Framework Codeigniter
- •••• JQuery
- •••• PHP Laravel Framework
- •••• Bootstrap Framework
- •••• Analysis Of Project
- ••• Process Improvement Flow

AWARDS RECEIVED

Website Developer: E-Commerce)

ADI HERNAWAN

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a web developer, my motivation when handling a project web application is not only doing but also providing an experience to my clients and their users.

Besides that, I am also ready to work outside my field, and I am ready to learn new things according to my future work.

WORK EXPERIENCE

IT Support (Internship)

PT Aisin Indonesia | Nov 2014 - 2015

- Troubleshooting problem computer
- Troubleshooting problem networking
- Installation software operating system

Freelance Web Developer

Sept 2019 - Current

- Analysis of project requirements creates algorithms, according to the program flow.
- Mobile-First, Responsive Design
- Cross Browser Testing & Debugging
- Improv the application according to scale analysis

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Bina Sarana Informatika

Sistem Informasi (D3) | Sept 2016 - Sept 2019

- GPA: 3.35
- Studied algorithms, programming language, and ethics
- Worked with building an application software

BWA Online Class Learning

BWA Store Marketplace | Okt 2020 - Jan 2021

- Studying Slicing UI Design to Web
- Studying Laravel Framework